{"data":[{"question":"Some people support the plan, but ___ are against it.","a":"much more","b":"many more","c":"any more","d":"no more","answer":"2","explain":"- Many\/much more: having a particular quality to a greater degree\u00a0\n+ Many more + countable noun (People) \n+ Much more+ uncountable noun \n- Any more: use in question or negative \n- No more= nothing, no change","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"That was a ___ shock.","a":"afraid","b":"frightened","c":"feared","d":"frightful","answer":"3","explain":"- Verb+ing\/verb + ed can play a role as adjective\u00a0\n+ Verb+ing: describe the effect that something has on your feelings, or on the feelings of people in general \n+ Verb+ ed: describe people's feelings. \n- \"Feared\" often goes with \"shock\" to describle something very frightened","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Our country has been a ___ one in the world.","a":"high-developed","b":"high-developing","c":"highly-developed","d":"highly-developing","answer":"3","explain":"- Highly-developed (adj): goes before a noun","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Australia and New Zealand are both ___ countries.","a":"English-spoken","b":"English-speaking","c":"spoken-English","d":"speaking-English","answer":"2","explain":"- English- speaking country: country used English as official language\u00a0\n- English- spoken (adjective)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"It is said that the thief was caught by a ___ boy.","a":"twelve-years old","b":"twelve years old","c":"twelve-years-old","d":"twelve-year-old","answer":"4","explain":"- twelve-year-old (adj): goes before a noun","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"The ___ music hall looks very luxurious.","a":"built new","b":"new built","c":"newly building","d":"newly built","answer":"4","explain":"- A Part participle standing before a noun can play role as an adjective to imply a completed action\u00a0\n- Adjectives modify nouns; adverbs modify verbs, adjectives, and other adverbs \n- Adverbs can modify adjectives, but an adjective cannot modify an adverb=&gt; adj + adv is not correct ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"The machine has ___ cover.","a":"a silver steel strong","b":"steel strong silver","c":"a silver strong steel","d":"a steel silver strong","answer":"3","explain":"- Adjective order: Opinion- size- age- shape-color- origin-material- purpose","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"France is ___ Japan in size.","a":"as equal","b":"equal to","c":"same like","d":"same as","answer":"2","explain":"- Be equal to sth: to be as good as something else","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Do you want ___ besides the golden bracelet?","a":"anything else","b":"some other","c":"everything else","d":"other any thing","answer":"1","explain":"- Else: used after words beginning with 'some-', 'every-', 'any-', and 'no-', and after question words): when you are referring to other things or people","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Ricky told us Mr. Kennedy moved. \"Yes, into a \u00a0___\"","a":"house of three story","b":"three story house","c":"house three storied","d":"house of three stories","answer":"4","explain":"- Plural form of noun: add \"s\" after noun\u00a0\n+ Note: Noun ends with \"y\", in plural form we change \"y\"-&gt; \"ies\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"}]}